Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- U, Series XXI
  - United Mission to Nepal publications
    - "Cluster Connection", 2009, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 13)
    - "The UMN Agroforestry Network Magazine", 1997-2000 (Box 252, Folder 16)
    - UMN publicity brochures and appeals for funds and personnel, 2003-2006, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 6)
    - UMN Christmas cards, leaflet alternative giving to UMN, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 7)
    - UMN Diary for 2002 (blank) (Box 253, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous UMN publications, incl. "Forgiveness and Reconciliation" (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - Other U
    - United Church of Canada: U-02.00.01 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - United Methodist Church, USA: U-03.00.01 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - United Church of Christ, Japan: U-04.00.01 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - United Nations: U-05.00.01/0001 - U-05.00.01/0004 - RESTRICTED, 1969-1987 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Urban Development: U-07.00.01/0001 - U-07.00.01/0029, 1989-1992 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - United Evangelical Lutheran Churches in India: U-09.00.01 (Box 156, Folder 3)
- V, Series XXII
  - Visitors: V-01.00.01 (Box 167, Folder 4-5)
  - Visitors: V-01.00.01 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Visas: V-02.00.01/0001 - V-02.00.01/0058 - RESTRICTED, 1958-1997 (Box 168, Folder 2-3)
  - V.S.O.: V-03.00.01 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Vacation houses:V-04.00.01 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Volunteer International Christian Service: V-05.00.01 - NOT LISTED IN SPREADSHEET
- W, Series XXIII
  - World Mission Prayer League: W-01.00.01 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Wesleyan Church: W-02.00.01 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - World Concern: W-03.00.01 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Women's Union Missionary Society: W-04.00.01 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - West Nepal: W-05.00.01 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - World Gospel Mission: W-07.00.01 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - World Brotherhood Exchange: W-08.00.01 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - World Council of Churches and CICARWS: W-06.00.01 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    See also F-06.00.01
  - Wiedenest Bibelschule: W-09.00.01 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - World Vision: W-10.00.01 - RESTRICTED (Box 169, Folder 2)
- Y, Series XXIV
  - Youth With a Mission (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - YWCA: correspondence: (Y-02.00), 1995-2007 (Box 232, Folder 3)
- Addendum - 2015, Series XXV
  - Organizational Records
    - UMN Constitution and By-laws, 2002-2012 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Annual reports/plans, 1985-1990 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      Extra copies received from offices of World Mission Prayer League
    - Annual Reports, 2005-2013 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 2011-2013 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Annual Audited Accounts, 2010 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Annual Audited Accounts, 2011-2013 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Budgets, 2009-2011 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Budgets, 2010-2013 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Plans, 2003-2015 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Directions, 2006-2013 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of Board of Directors, Executive Committee, Board of Managers, 1952-1990 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      Extra copies received from World Mission Prayer League offices.
    - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors, 2007 May-2009 Nov (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors, 2010 Apr-2012 May (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of UMN Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 May-2013 Nov (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the General Assembly, 2007 May-2013 May (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Publications
    - Video Productions: AIDS/HIV awareness, Interfaith Networks, 2009-2014 (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Brochures and Leaflets: General and Strategy, 2003-2012 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters, 2005-2013 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Friends of Tansen, 2007-2013 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Friends of Okhaldhunga, 2005-2013 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Cards, no date (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Partner Profiles, 2012 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Prayer Notes & Cards, 2006-2013 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Calendars & Pocket Planners, 2010-2013 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Food Security and Hunger Survey in Nepal, 2004 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - 2010 Calendar (Box OV2)
    - Posters: Set of 4: Education, Health, Peacebuilding, Sustainable Livlihoods, Mission Statement, Fullness of Life Model, Values, Strategic Plan (2 Types), Strategic Plan, Set of 3 HIV & AIDS Posters; Handwashing, 2011-2013 (Box OV2)
    - Posters, map, calendar, large photograph (Box OV3)
    - Posters mounted on cardboard (Gorkha District map, "Fifty Years in God's Hands", "UMN will be involved in...", "UMN will work through..." (Box OV3)
    - Scrapbooks and magazines (Box OV3)
    - Oversize photograph labeled "Top of Liglig, Gorkha at the beginning of UMN work, 1957" Maps of Nepal and UMN, 1957, no date (Box OVd-2)
  - Program Materials
    - English language
      - HIV/AIDS Materials: Training Manual, Information Cards, 2012, no date (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - Manual of Emergency Treatment Protocols for Certified Medical Assistants and Health Assistants, 1998 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Trauma Counseling Manuals, 2001-2003 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Nepali language
      - Poultry Managment and Animal Health, no date (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Educational Plan Diary, no date (Box 259, Folder 6)
      - Educational Material for Children, no date (Box 259, Folder 7)
      - HIV/AIDS Educational Materials, no date (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Food and Plant Management Materials, no date (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Disaster Planning Materials, no date (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Communal Peace and Development Materials, no date (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Road Safety, no date (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Pathways to Good Governance, no date (Box 260, Folder 6)
      - Christian Family Life Education, no date (Box 260, Folder 7)
      - Handbook for Pyschological Diagnoses, no date (Box 260, Folder 8)
      - Memory of Mugu and Collection of Songs, no date (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - 15 Steps Against Human Trafficking, no date (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Infection Control for Dental Clinics, no date (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Consulting Directory, no date (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Materials, no date (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Materials, no date (Box 261, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous Materials, no date (Box 261, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Materials: Three Oversized Educational Documents, no date (Box OV2)
  - Collected Materials
    - Book: Life in Okhaldhunga Community Hospital by Erlend Berge, 2008 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - 2014 Calendar produced by UMN paratner Chandvamukh Club (Box 261, Folder 9)